♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
[gunshots]
[groans]
[Samir, in English] I was attacked.
[Artem, in English] You were attacked?
[in English] Identities?
[in English] Friends of Atoy.
[Samir, in English] We must find
his family, right now.
There were three men here, collecting.
[Olga] Those three men
you talked to, they're enemies!
[henchman 1] They're here.
[Martina] They're at Olga's house now,
and hopefully by lunchtime,
we'll have Ibyang.
[in English] Finally, some good news.
- [spritzing]
- [both screaming]
- [screaming]
- [Olga] Ibyang! Come on, hurry!
[Olga] Come on, come on! Hurry, hurry!
[Samir, in English] We need that woman
and her daughter!
[in English] Or that man will not talk!
[in English] We can mimic
the woman's voice,
and we can make her say anything we want.
- [Olga shouts]
- [man grunts]
- Ibyang! Come on.
- [groaning]
No one make the wrong move!
[Charmi] Move!
Go there! Hurry!
[Atoy, in English] What--
What did you do to them?
[Samir, in English] They are safe.
[in English] I will tell you
where the laptop is.
[in English] You'd better
tell me the truth.
[Audrey, in English] I need
to talk to Atoy first.
Then together,
we'll tell Janine the truth.
[Cita] Olga, what happened?
Why did Ame have to take the child away?
Is there a problem?
[sighs] I've been calling Atoy
for a while now.
My love, what are you going to tell Atoy?
You can tell me.
Atoy is Ibyang's real father.
PREVIOUSLY
[music fades]
[Viktor, in English] Bring them all here.
[in English] We will dismantle it…
and we have men that can check the engines
and parts to see
if we can salvage anything.
[in English] If not, I have a machine
that can make it into scrap metal.
[in English] You have a junkyard?
[in Russian] Yes.
[in English] In San Rodolfo, Bulacan.
[Viktor, in English] Yes. I'm here now.
[in English] But tomorrow, maybe not.
[in English] Yes. Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[in English] So…
[in English] You are the one
that attacked me in my office, huh?
[music swells]
[suave theme music playing]
[in English] What?!
So, Atoy is Ibyang's real father?
And you're her mother?
So that means you're the parents?
No, no, no, not like that.
It's not like that.
It's-- It's just Atoy who's the parent.
What did you say?
Aren't you the mother?
[pensive music playing]
I don't understand what you're saying.
[Olga] Um…
Don't be mad, huh.
I'm not really
Ibyang's real mother.
[music fades]
What?!
[clears throat] So,
you're a fake mother?
Something like that, yes.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [Olga sighs]
I auditioned with Ma'am Martina
and Red Regalia. [inhales]
They hired me
to pretend to be Ibyang's mother.
The pay is quite big.
I needed the money.
That's terrible.
How could you bear to deceive the child?!
Don't you have a conscience?!
[in English] I can't believe this.
[in English] You're only beautiful
on the outside,
but you're very ugly inside!
[in English] How could you do this to me?
[Emerson] Huh?
So that means you're Red's employee!
- You're Red's minion!
- [Olga] No!
No, no. It's not like that-- [sighs]
[sighs] I'm sorry.
[Cita scoffs]
It's just work.
That's all it is.
It's just my job, promise.
[Olga] Nothing else.
That's why I'm here,
because I found out
that Atoy is the real father of Ibyang,
and Madam Martina plans to take her away.
And how are we supposed to believe you?
For all we know, you and the Regalias
have another plan!
I can't take that thought
out of your mind. I'm sorry.
But I'm here to set things right.
You know, honestly,
I even wanted to adopt the child.
Because Ibyang has become dear to me.
But then I found out that Atoy
is actually Ibyang's real father.
That's why I'm here now.
So, what now?
Atoy isn't here.
Actually, Atoy is missing.
If Atoy isn't here,
maybe don't tell anyone yet.
Let's keep it between us for now.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[grunts]
- [groans]
- [in English] That's
for attacking me in my office.
- [pensive music playing]
- [Atoy inhales]
[in English] But I must admit.
[in English] I am impressed.
[in English] You single-handedly
infiltrated the embassy.
[cackles]
Bravo!
[pensive continues playing]
[in English] But did you think
you could get away with this?
[in English] If you don't want anything
to happen to the woman and child,
you will tell me!
[in English] Where is the laptop?!
[in English] Do you want to know
where the laptop is?
[in English] I need proof of life first.
[in English] You want proof of life?
Hmm?
[in English] How about I just take yours?
‪[grunts]
[grunting and groaning]
[grunts]
[Lily sobs]
[Lily, in English] Sir, please.
Stop. Stop. Stop, sir!
[Lily, in English] Sir, please have mercy.
[groans]
[Viktor, in English] How dare you
talk to me, traitor!
[in English] No, no, no, no!
Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
[in English] No, no, no. Don't hurt her!
[Atoy, in English] I will stop.
I will stop.
[in English] I will give you
what you want!
[in English] I will tell you
- where the laptop is!
- [Lily gasps]
[Viktor, in English] Samir, that's enough.
[in English] We need him alive.
[in English] He is a professional.
[in English] Military or police.
[in English] I'm sure
he's trained to take any pain.
[in English] No matter what we do,
no matter what torture,
he will not talk.
[in English] And what will we do with him?
[in English] His people
will be looking for him.
[in English] We need
to take them both out!
[in English] But ultimately,
we have to get him to talk!
[music swells]
[in English] Wait a minute, huh.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
[in English] If Atoy is the father, hmm…
who is the mother?
I don't know.
[pensive music playing]
Atoy dated some women before,
but nothing serious.
From what I know, the only one
who really mattered to him was Audrey.
And Audrey already had
a child with Atoy, Janine.
OMG, Miss C!
[suspicious music playing]
Aren't Ibyang and Janine the same age?
[Cita] Oh?
Oh, then maybe Ibyang
is also Audrey's daughter.
Maybe they were fraternal twins before,
just separated by circumstances.
You, Emerson, you've been watching
too many TV series reruns!
Audrey and Atoy never said
their child had a twin, right?!
I don't know about you!
- Fraternal, because…
- Mmm, because--
And Madam Martina also never mentioned
that Ibyang had a twin.
[sighs]
What if Audrey doesn't know this?
Oh no.
Audrey needs to know this.
She's here.
[music swells]
Atoy.
[music fades]
- [Atoy] Lily.
- [Lily] Atoy.
[Atoy] Take it, take it.
Where did you get--
Take it.
- [tense music playing]
- [Lily straining]
[Atoy] Open it.
[Lily strains]
Open it.
[Lily] Wait.
[Atoy] Did you get it?
[Lily strains]
That, that.
[panting]
Open it.
Wait.
[heavy breathing]
Wait, it's locked.
I've hacked complicated
computer systems before.
What's a cell phone password anyway?
Sister Ame told me why you're here now.
Maybe…
[sentimental music playing]
…we should practice how to fight.
Mmm.
I have an idea!
When Tatoy comes back,
let's ask him to teach us
how to fight, so…
we can defend ourselves.
So, what? You in?
We'll deal with the bad people.
[music fades]
- [imitating fighting sounds]
- [light music playing]
You're funny too, huh?
But are you sure you can fight?
Of course.
Once I learn,
I'll defend Mama
from those
who are chasing her.
Mama? You have a mama now?
Where?
[music fades]
[Janine] Ah! I know.
In your imagination?
No, a real mama!
She found me. Mmm.
Now we're the same.
[pensive music playing]
Okay, now we're the same.
Daddy. You have one too?
Uh, well…
Tatoy.
Here we go again.
Your real father, your blood relative!
[music fades]
[sniffles, then gasps]
- There. There, it's done.
- [tense music playing]
Ready?
Okay, fine.
Dial it.
- [in English] 0-9-0…
- [Lily mumbles]
- 7…
- Hm-mm.
- 6-4-3-2-2-1.
- Uh-huh.
[Lily] There.
[phone ringing]
[music swells]
Hello?
Ibyang. Ibyang!
Ibyang, this is Atoy.
Tatoy?!
[intense music playing]
Ibyang, Ibyang, I need your help.
I--I--I was captured.
I'm here in a car junkyard
in… in San Rodolfo, Bulacan.
San Rodolfo, hurry.
Write it down.
The owner is Viktor Petrov.
[tense music playing]
He's-- He's the ambassador
of the Zahran Embassy.
Call my boss, Mercado.
Call him. Tell him where I am.
Y-Yes, yes, yes.
Uh, car junkyard, San Rodolfo, Bulacan,
owned by Viktor Petrov.
Find Boss Mercado.
[Atoy] Okay, thank you.
Ibyang, Ibyang, don't--
don't ever call this number again.
Did you hear me?
Do you understand, huh?
Okay, Tatoy.
[keys drop and jingle]
Call Mercado. Call--
[tense music playing]
[in English] What are you doing?
[in English] Who are you talking to?
But--
That was Daddy, right?
I want to talk to him.
Call him again!
He said it's prohibited!
What do you mean prohibited?!
- Oh, it's prohibited. Prohibited.
- But you talked to him yourself!
He said it's not allowed.
- That's unfair, Ibyang!
- Janine, please. Janine--
- No-- Don't, Janine--
- Ibyang!
[grunts]
- [vendor] Thank you, miss.
- [Karla] Thank you.
Karla.
- Hi.
- Gavin!
I gotta go now.
Our breakfast will get cold. All right.
Breakfast with Uno?
Why did he get involved?
[in English] I don't know. Maybe
you're having breakfast together.
Looks like you're really close to him.
Who is that Uno really?
[in English] Where did he come from?
What is he doing here?
Uno and Atoy are workmates.
- So is he also a tailor?
- [quirky music playing]
New shop assistant?
Why do you have
so many questios about him?
It's because he is so arrogant,
acting like he is somebody big.
And he's being way too familiar with you.
So what?
[quirky sting]
Why don't you say all those
observations right to my face?
That makes you look like
a total keyboard warrior.
You're acting like a basher. Huh?
[smirks]
Do you know this woman?
I'll ask my friend.
[Uno] You're friend is really
something, huh?
[Uno smirks]
Hey!
Bro, I will not hurt you.
Why are you hiding?
What happened to your friend, Karla?
[Karla] Gavin!
Why are you hiding?
Cha! Do you know her?
[Cha] No.
[tense music playing]
[Uno] Hey!
- Hey, are you okay?
- [in English] I have to warn Aunt Audrey.
My dad's goon is here.
Where?
[in English] Nobody was talking. I--
[in English] Liar. I heard a voice.
[in English] He was-- [sniffles]
He was just…
probably talking in his sleep, that's all.
[groans]
[sobs, in English] Please don't.
Please, just please stop.
[pensive music playing]
[Lily sobs]
[in English] You know,
people call me many things.
[in English] They call me a monster.
[in English] Sometimes they say
I'm the devil.
[in English] But you know,
they're all wrong.
[tense music playing]
[in English] You see,
the devil brings temptation.
[in English] I bring certainty.
[in English] Tomorrow,
both of you will die.
[music swells]
[Lily sobbing]
[music fades]
[Lily] Atoy, is this how
we're going to die?
I didn't even get to see my child again.
[pensive music playing]
[sobbing]
[Lily] Am I going to die here?
[melodramatic music playing]
That won't happen, Lily.
[sobbing]
Just trust, please.
They will save us.
[dramatic music playing]
Do you know this man?
Who is he?
[man 1] No!
- [henchman 1] Are you sure?
- [man 2] But
he often hangs out
at the basketball court.
Maybe he's there.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Let's go, bro.
- Let's go.
[suspicious music playing]
That's Gavin!
You know, Audrey needs to know this.
- I'll just call her. She's here--
- Wait, wait!
[in English] Yes, my love?
What if she's not the real mother?
Right? Think about it. Atoy is handsome.
It's not impossible that many women
wanted to get pregnant by him. Right?
[Emerson] That's possible, possible.
You have a point.
You have a point, here.
Well, actually, Atoy is really secretive
when it comes to women.
So, only Atoy should know about this.
Because only Atoy could possibly know
who Ibyang's real mother is.
So, if possible,
while Atoy isn't here yet,
no one should say anything to anyone.
Even…
Even about me being a fake mother.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [heavy breathing]
I want to be the one to tell
Atoy myself about his other child.
Don't worry.
We'll make sure no one finds out
about you being a fake mother,
my love.
[in English] Sorry, I overheard.
[pensive music playing]
Were you talking about
Janine and Atoy?
Uh, uh…
Uh, I was just telling Olga that
your and Janine's situation is dangerous.
So, you should stay here while
waiting for Atoy to return.
You-- You're Olga?
[Audrey] You're Ibyang's mother?
Yes, I am.
‪[Audrey sighs]
‪[Olga sighs]
Audrey, right?
In fairness,
Atoy really knows how to choose.
You're beautiful, girl.
[Audrey chuckles]
[in English] Thank you.
[gentle music playing]
Uh, where is Ibyang?
She's in the room.
Um, we're staying here too,
until Atoy comes back.
Not that you asked,
but I also had a slight past with Atoy.
- Um, we were supposed to date before.
- [whimsical music playing]
But it didn't happen.
Ah, really?
[sighs, in English] What a small world.
Can you believe it?
You're Ibyang's mother.
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] It's a small world after all.
Junkyard of cars.
San Rodolfo, Bulacan.
There's Viktor Petrov.
- Ibyang? Uh…
- San Rodolfo, Bulacan.
Are you hungry or possessed?
You're saying so much.
I should not forget it.
Tatoy called.
I spoke to him!
My God! Thank God!
Atoy is alive?
Ibyang, what else did he say, huh?
And where is he? Is he okay?
What else? What else did he say?
He said he needs help
because he was captured.
[gasps]
He said he's at--
[suspicious music playing]
At the car junkyard at…
San Viktor-- I mean!
San Rodolfo!
In Bulacan.
With Viktor Petrov.
[music fades]
V-Viktor Petrov?
[tense music playing]
So, he's being held
by the ambassador of Zahran!
Is that what he told you?
He didn't say that
he was the one who captured him.
Let's call the police!
[Emerson] No, uh…
The police can't just get in there easily.
There are a lot of procedures
to go follow.
He said we should find his boss,
Mercado!
[Olga] Mercado?
[in English] As in Jennylyn Mercado?
Ah-- What's that?
He has a celebrity boss? Why?
- I'm confused.
- No, uh…
His boss is tougher than the police.
We need to talk to Uno.
He's Mercado's man.
[in English] Auntie, we have to go.
I saw Daddy's men.
They're looking for us.
[in English] W-We can't leave.
[stammers] What if Atoy comes back here?
He won't find anyone.
Uh, just stay here.
No one from here will point you out.
Gavin, do you know what they look like?
My friend is the new town captain.
I'll tell her to drive them away.
[rousing music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[intense music playing]
Miss, what did they say?
Will they save Atoy?
Yes. He's talking to his boss inside.
They said they'll send an extraction team.
You know, if Uno is bringing anyone
to their operation, it should be me.
Oh, oops! It fell.
UP NEXT
- You're peeking, bro.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
[Mongki] Our boys said Atoy is missing.
I wish we were the ones who kidnapped him.
But whoever did it, I hope…
I hope they kill Atoy.
[Lily] Where are you taking us?
[in English] Didn't I tell you that today
is the day you'll die?
[in English] And I'm a man of my word!
[in English] So, prepare to die. Let's go!
[in English] What are we waiting for?
- [Lily] Atoy, what now, Atoy?
- [in English] Bring them! Let's go.
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias